{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5430","name":"Ready Player One","address":"407 E Fort St. ","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Badgharb LLC","licenseNumber":"220236","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.04252,42.33302","geojson":{"id":"5430","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.0425205189999,42.3330162770001]},"properties":{"name":"Ready Player One","owner":"Badgharb LLC","address":"407 E Fort St. ","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"220236","establishmentid":"5430","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/24/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"964","name":"Bouzouki Club","address":"432 E Lafayette Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4681","name":"Dream Club","address":"440 E Lafayette Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1089","name":"Loco Bar & Grill","address":"454 E Lafayette Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"579","name":"Jacoby's German Biergarten","address":"624 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1191","name":"Niki's Pizzeria","address":"735-37 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4682","name":"Niki's Lounge","address":"735 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"704","name":"Detroiter Bar","address":"655 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5275","name":"Legends Gentleman's Club - PEMC LLC","address":"415 E Congress St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4183","name":"Mix Bricktown","address":"641 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3862","name":"Good People Popcorn","address":"633 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43611","inspectionDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-401.14","violationDescription":"Raw animal FOODS that are cooked using a NON-CONTINUOUS COOKING process shall be: \r\n(A) Subject to an initial heating process that is no longer than sixty minutes in      duration; (P)   \r\n(B) Immediately after initial heating, cooled according to the time and temperature      parameters specified for cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) under ¶ 3-501.14(A); (P)   \r\n(C) After cooling, held frozen or cold, as specified for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) under ¶ 3-501.16(A)(2);(P)   \r\n(D) Prior to sale or service, cooked using a process that heats all parts of the FOOD to a time/temperature specified in paragraph 3-401.11(A); (P)   \r\n(E) Cooled according to the time and temperature parameters specified for cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) under ¶ 3-501.14(A) if not either hot held as specified under ¶ 3-501.16(A), served immediately, or held using time as a public health control as specified under §3-501.19 after complete cooking; (P) and   \r\n(F) Stored as follows:  \r\n(1) After initial heating but prior to cooking as specified under ¶ (D) of this section,     separate from ready-to-eat foods as specified under ¶ 3-302.11; (Pf) and\r\n(2) After initial heating, but prior to complete cooking, marked or otherwise         identified as foods that must be cooked as specified under ¶ (D) of this section         prior to being offered for sale or service. (Pf) The food may be identified in any        effective manner provided that the marking system is disclosed to the        regulatory authority upon request.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41455","inspectionDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]},{"inspectionid":"40116","inspectionDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]},{"inspectionid":"40106","inspectionDate":"2017-09-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"BAR","subLocation":"AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Prep sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"Covered waste container","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5430"}}